[{"answer": "What time is it", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Time", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend or Zoey.  Which ever you like", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " That's funny.  We both have Z names", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Do you ask all your clients questions", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Do you ask all your clients questions", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "So you like me", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How do you know I'm a good person", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How do you know I'm a good person", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "All men and women fit together.  Hell, even some men fit together", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I see", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No, I do", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How could I resist your invitation", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "So what have you been doing here", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't know...it connects the two vaults", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Also Swiss, but this one is a Poseidon", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "But this entry way is too small to get the platen out.  We have a lot of merchandise in there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's impossible", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know what to do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's not impossible.  Everyone knows what to do", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You don't need to know shit.  Just get into the vault and we'll do the rest", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How could I resist your invitation", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "So what have you been doing here", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know...it connects the two vaults", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Also Swiss, but this one is a Poseidon", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "But this entry way is too small to get the platen out.  We have a lot of merchandise in there", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It's impossible", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't know what to do", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's not impossible.  Everyone knows what to do", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You don't need to know shit.  Just get into the vault and we'll do the rest", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, I wouldn't want to do that", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Got it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Right.  When you tell me, I'll open it up", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No sir.  Your best bet is to get these bars melted down in that place or that place", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Or that place", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You know.  Something to cover this with. It'll look kind of conspicuous leaving the bank with a platten of gold", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Police?!  What do you mean they know what we're up too", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " What's your girlfriends name", "docId": "Killing-Zoe.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "my friend. ", "qsentId": 44}]